=Love Actually=
(Shanghai)
(Daily Gatherings Beyond the Love House)
(Zhou Youling's Recording Perspective)
Who is this?
(Xuan playing tennis)
Hello.
Who are you?
(Xiaowen letting loose)
Why did you come alone?
(Liu temporarily absent due to work)
(Defeated)
(Just watch, bro)
You haven't played tennis
for quite a while, right?
Just ease into it first.
You need to adjust.
(Still got my skills)
Good.
We're done playing.
It's over.
I'm soaked in sweat.
Feels like I just took a shower.
It's basically like I took a whole bath.
Big Bro barely broke a sweat.
I did, I'm all sweaty.
Your hair isn't wet.
Your hair is completely dry.
My hair is dry,
but my body is wet.
Xuan and I are drenched
as if we showered.
Let's go home.
Cooking.
Start cooking.
(Chef Xuan's Menu: Tomato Beef Brisket)
I'll make tomato beef brisket
and cola chicken wings.
What are you making?
Garlic Wagyu.
(Chef Zhou's Menu: Garlic Wagyu)
Hua Diao
(Chef Zhou's Menu: Garlic Wagyu, Hua Diao Sashimi)
sashimi,
(Chef Zhou's Menu: Garlic Wagyu, Hua Diao Sashimi, Black Truffle Fried Rice)
and black truffle fried rice.
I ordered takeout.
Is that Peking roast duck?
(Xiaowen's Dish Today)
I brought it from Beijing.
What about you?
I'll be the helper.
Peeling garlic and washing vegetables
for you.
Garlic-peeling girl.
(Garlic-peeling girl)
Okay.
Garlic-peeling girl.
Let's start.
Okay.
Who said eggs need washing?
The eggs need to be washed.
Eggs need to be washed?
Why wash eggs?
Of course, they need to be washed.
There is chicken poop
and bacteria on the outside.
You just ate a lot of...
You ate a lot of chicken poop.
Tired?
Not tired.
Babe.
Do the eggs need to be washed,
Babe?
(Hehehe)
Who said this?
I don't know.
Babe said it.
Which babe?
Your babe said it.
Wash it.
Wash.
Do you still need this?
Babe, I think we don't need it.
(Babe)
Babe, why are you frozen here?
Babe.
I don't know what to do right now.
Everything is done.
I'm just waiting for my meat.
Then stir-fry this
and it'll be ready.
Marinate this.
Marinate the chicken wings.
How to marinate? Teach me.
Shut up.
Enough.
No, I won't.
Babe.
All ingredients prepped.
I'm about to start.
There's water.
What's wrong?
There's water here.
This lemon
is from our own tree.
I picked it myself.
It smells so good.
Three, two, one.
Come on, Jia Peixuan.
(Love feeding)
This pancake isn't quite right.
It's a bit thick.
Way too thick.
And the sauce isn't right either.
The sauce is a bit too sweet.
My second dish,
cola chicken wings.
Xuan is just amazing.
What can you do?
She can cook, look beautiful,
and surf too.
How are you going to compliment me?
I'll knock your teeth out.
There's one standing back there.
Completely silent.
If you film me, I'll film you too.
Smells delicious.
(Cola chicken wings, Tomato beef brisket)
Looks really good.
Let's look at our garlic-peeling girl.
What?
How many times have we cooked in total?
How many times has Zhou Youling cooked?
I cooked once.
When?
Today.
Now.
Now. It's happening right now.
Come on.
How many times have you cooked?
I've cooked the same number
of times as you.
You're always one time short.
I helped cook today.
(Peeled garlic, in a quiet, weak voice)
I peeled the garlic.
Sea urchin egg fried rice.
You added sea urchin this time.
This man
got something.
He looks terrible in my shots.
(Xiaowen's POV: Bossy CEO flips the wok)
(Hungry crowd)
All waiting for the food to be ready.
We're in a row.
Yeah, lining up.
One, two, three.
Four.
Relay.
Got some skills.
(Deluxe Egg Fried Rice)
(Today's Dinner)
Today,
Xuan and Youling
cooked most of the feast.
Liu and I just helped out.
You did all the chopping.
Today, the weird duo is kitchen helpers.
Yes.
Let's eat.
Time to eat!
Welcome.
Welcome, Xuan.
Welcome, Xuan and Xiaowen.
Why aren't you welcoming me?
You...
The first time we met...
The two of us welcome the two of them.
(Meme Reappears)
She had nothing.
You didn't give my...
Her drink.
You just took it
and put it on the floor.
Sorry.
Start over.
One more time.
It's okay.
Alright, welcome Xuan and Xiaowen.
Thank you.
Thank you, Big Bro and Liu, for...
For...
Right, your warm hospitality.
Your invitation.
Thanks for inviting us, Big Bro.
So hilarious.
Okay.
Okay, come on.
Let's dig in.
None of us has energy left for talking.
Let's eat.
Bye-bye, see you later.
Bye.
(After-dinner leisure time)
What's this?
Slippers.
You're too...
I can't do this with this leg.
Be a bit steadier.
Okay.
The four of us.
(After-dinner game: Who's the Mole?)
Who's the Mole?
Everyone draw one card.
Okay.
You guys go first.
Tap the screen to draw a card.
Check it yourself.
Don't show us.
(If You Are the One, If You Are the One,
If You Are the One, One Out of a Hundred)
The winner goes first.
Let the winner go first.
Four words.
It can be used to describe a state.
Is it an idiom?
This word has multiple numbers.
(If You Are the One, If You Are the One,
If You Are the One, One Out of a Hundred)
Three, two, one.
(Unanimous Approval)
Once I said it...
What's yours?
One Out of a Hundred.
If You Are the One.
What's the connection...
What's the connection between these two?
Right.
No.
Both One Out of a Hundred
and If You Are the One
are dating shows, right?
I messed up.
I was going to say that too.
I thought yours was one in ten thousand.
Let me think.
Just that one, Big Bro.
Your mouth...
This is a piece of cake for him.
This is a treat for him, not punishment.
It's more like a reward for you.
This isn't a punishment at all.
Did you remember
the clip we filmed on the last episode?
Which scene did you two perform?
Bossy CEO.
The bossy CEO says,
"Girl,
you've caught my eye."
Liu, you just make up any line
for Big Bro to say.
Let me think.
What line would totally break him?
You have to make him break.
Seize the opportunity.
Cheesy lines.
(Escaping the premeditated scene)
Listen,
I'll allow you to like me.
I think that works.
Listen.
(Finalize lines: Listen, I'll allow you to like me)
I'll allow you to like me.
(Can't wait)
This works.
Listen, I'll allow you to like me.
It really sounds like
something he'd say.
It's good.
Come on, Zhou Youling.
What?
Wait.
Get a closer camera angle.
(Camera Ready)
(Jia Peixuan's Recording Perspective)
Action.
This...
(Jia Peixuan's Recording Perspective)
Listen,
I'll allow you to like me.
He's taking the penalty,
but the three of us
are the ones suffering.
The three of us.
The three of us are such silly geese.
I had this coming.
Asking for trouble.
(After-dinner game: Word Stack)
Everyone adds one word each round.
Come on.
Xuan goes first.
You first.
To.
Today.
Tonight, the two of us
don't have much money to get some food.
He didn't say that much.
You added too many words.
You added two words.
Got caught.
Liu.
Have Liu do a cute, clingy act.
No way.
You love this, don't you?
(Mercilessly uncovered)
This is a treat for you.
What do you mean?
It turned into your
exclusive punishment.
Really.
I thought of one.
It's a bit gross.
Go ahead.
Even I can't...
Come closer.
Otherwise, the camera can't catch it.
You can come a bit closer.
Do you like me, sweetie?
I'm coming.
You're rewarding him again.
It's fine.
Ear.
Another reward for him.
I like it.
I can't take it.
In your opinion,
what behaviors turn women off?
When meeting
cringey people,
you'll also feel... Right?
Yeah.
I thought you would say
(The one who asked me to call her sister)
asking you to call me sister
is such a turn-off.
Well.
He said, "Do you have some weird kink?"
"What's this old-fashioned mindset
coming from?'
But then later, he was enjoying
calling her that.
Really enjoy it.
We can feel it.
He kept calling her that.
Being his true self.
No.
He was being his true self
when calling you sister.
Earlier, he said,
"Do you have some weird kick?"
But he was probably thinking
you share the same weird quirks as me.
So funny.
I have a question for you two.
What things
do guys do
that totally turn you off?
Asking if the perfume smells good.
(The one who asked
if the perfume smells good)
No, just kidding.
(After-dinner game: Never Have I Ever)
What does it mean?
First, say one thing...
Just say one thing
you've experienced that no one else has.
I can say...
For example, I...
I've done something.
I experienced something. Anything works.
If none of you have done it...
If you haven't done it,
put down one finger
At the end, all fingers are down...
Whoever puts them all down first loses.
I can play the trumpet.
I can play the clarinet.
I can play it too.
I can play scales.
I can play the piano.
Then I can do it too.
I can also...
That counts?
(Sly fox enters the chat)
That doesn't count.
I can handle the piano keys.
He can only play short little tunes.
I can make a sound.
I can even play the tune of
"Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star."
Fine.
I admit defeat.
Next one.
If we all share this experience,
you put one finger down.
No one put any fingers down?
All of you can play the piano?
Right.
You put one finger down.
So annoyed.
It's my turn, right?
I have a child.
Going all out right away.
Bring up the thing like this.
You hit us with your biggest move
right away.
Starting with a big move right away.
This game.
Well,
I'll save you.
Okay, save me.
I got my ears pierced.
This works.
Then I have three left.
I ate roast duck in Nanjing.
I've eaten it.
I've eaten it too.
I've got this in the bag.
What to do?
Help me.
No, you're already lost.
I'm already lost?
Just say anything.
You say one thing
and she says one thing.
After I say it, you're out.
My number of exes
is under three.
Does that equal three?
Not equal to three.
I can surf.
Do I count as someone who can surf?
Of course, you can surf.
Yes.
Yes, you can.
Therefore, I picked something
only we two have done.
What to do?
No more rewards for Big Bro.
No more satisfying him.
How about this, Big Bro?
You randomly pick a male guest
among all these guys,
and leave a comment
in his comment section.
Okay.
They won't mind.
Have him send an emoji sticker.
In Ji Yu's comment section,
I drop a Lurking emoji.
Okay.
Think carefully.
I won't get tangled up in this scheme.
You chose it yourself.
He chose it himself.
It has nothing to do with me.
They made me do this penalty.
No.
We didn't.
I didn't tell him to pick Ji Yu.
Just asked him to post an emoji sticker.
Pick anyone to send it.
But he's going to pick Ji Yu.
Right.
He chose to send it to Ji Yu himself.
I just randomly
picked Ji Yu.
I scrolled and Ji Yu showed up first.
Okay.
We believe it.
Finished.
Take a screenshot.
(Successfully posted)
Just feels like...
He is really something else.
Won't hold back
from escalating everything.
(After-dinner game: Idiom Chain)
Let's play Idiom Chain.
This is hard.
Come on.
As steady as a rock.
There's always someone better.
Old friends amid rivers and mountains.
People come and go.
Vast ocean.
Castles in the air.
This is so hard.
Lou.
Lou...
Hug my wife.
Lou.
Go ahead and hug.
He even said, "Hug my wife".
Hug my wife.
How about "fish that escaped the net"?
Then you hug first.
Hug first.
You hug your...
Okay.
The fish that escaped the net.
Wait.
This part won't be suitable
for broadcast.
Can't air it.
(Bonus: Zhou Youling's Perspective)
Come on.
Ten seconds.
Thirty seconds.
Can you sing this?
Okay.
(Love Diary)
(Attention Seeker)
Grab a meal together after work.
(Born for the camera)
I made dinner plans with Xuan today.
Is this expression okay?
It's fine, as long as you...
She keeps saying I'm cringey.
Am I really?
Just a little cheeky sometimes.
Happy every day.
Enjoy the moment.
Next time, take me to work out.
Let's meet at the gym next time.
Take me to work out my shoulders.
So interesting.
I'll keep the camera on the whole time.
I won't let you rest.
If there's a camera,
I'll instantly get energetic.
(A blogger's instinct)
I'll sponsor you a memory card.
Okay.
Keep recording nonstop.
Sure.
I'll record the whole time.
(Dug a hole for myself)
I won't stop recording halfway.
Sister, I'm relying on you.
Leave it to me.
I'll shape your body.
I plan to draw a picture for Youling.
I'll give it to him at dinner tomorrow.
Engage in eight full hours of sketch...
Creation.
We'll split the work.
Mr. Lu will draft the outline,
and I'll fill in the colors.
Leave the coloring to me.
Creating in progress.
I'll handle all colored parts.
Actually, Mr. Lu draws very well.
(Mutual compliments)
Actually, Ruita is better at coloring.
Finished.
I also made a photo frame like this.
(Meeting again)
Hi.
Ruita agreed to work out
with Xuan in a few days.
They'll train back,
(For real?)
then legs,
with extra glute work.
Is this true?
(Good job, Babe)
Okay.
Go for it.
(Nominal coach)
Hit full body.
Xuan will guide my workout.
(Real coach)
What's for breakfast today?
Hamburgers.
Making Crabby Patty.
Crabby Patty.
Who cooks on time every day?
It's Ruita's fitness coach.
(Exclusive to Ruita)
Now I'm watching the watch-along.
We're heading out for dinner after work.
We're even shipping a couple in the car.
(Shipping ourselves)
That's amazing.
Who is this?
This girl is very pretty.
That guy is quite handsome too.
Do you know him?
Seems a bit like you.
I don't know.
That's amazing.
But I feel like his style
is quite similar to mine.
Who is this?
(The male lead himself)
Sort of similar.
Really looks alike.
(100% similarity)
Is his name Lu Bingkun?
I don't know him.
Good morning, everyone.
(Going to a debate)
We are on our way to the debate.
Ruita (Wang Yi) will be the host.
(Nonsense)
I'm not the host.
I'm a listener
from the friendly side of the debate.
Today's debate topic is...
(Go ahead)
(Today's topic: Does happiness come from certainty or uncertainty?)
Does happiness come from certainty
or uncertainty?
I think happiness
comes from uncertainty.
I am on the affirmative side.
I'm on the opposite side of you.
You're on the opposite side of me.
So what is your argument?
My argument is that
in many cases, happiness
is encountered unexpectedly.
You have no expectations whatsoever.
(Opposing argument: Happiness is unexpected)
So, uncertainty
brings joy,
happiness, and surprise.
Now it's your turn, affirmative side.
Why does happiness come from certainty?
(Affirmative argument: Happiness is based on certainty)
Happiness is based on certainty.
It might come from uncertainty.
However,
uncertainty is a collection
of small frustrations.
What makes you feel at ease
and allows you to experience happiness
comes from a stable life.
So with a relatively stable life,
you'll have the ability and time
to feel those uncertainties.
So, happiness comes from certainty.
(Convinced)
What you said seems to make sense.
Alright, it's over.
We finished our task today.
(Dinner after the debate)
Eating a lamb spine hot pot.
Someone came out wearing hotel slippers.
Very relaxed.
On a very relaxing day.
Today, his eyes were even red
from the debate.
I got red-eyed from the arguing.
I got all worked up.
(Ruita's favorite lamb spine)
Eating my favorite lamb spine!
The bone is a heart shape.
My favorite chicken cartilage.
Time for lunch!
Model.
Just an hour and a half
after breakfast,
someone is here for lunch.
I didn't exercise today,
but after eating,
I can do some exercise.
She means
to take a couple of breaths.
That's not true.
I'm serious.
I'm going to do some
ab crunches today, okay?
I'll record it later.
(Closing Eyes)
Do you believe me?
(Eyes closed, unconditional trust)
BK (Lu Bingkun).
Freshly tossed salad.
Let's copy this dish later.
Okay, Mr. Lu?
Sure.
I'll make one five times
bigger than this.
(Super double)
Five times bigger, eat it yourself.
Have some apple.
Thank you.
You do like apples.
Big meal.
I almost mistook this
for a pig's trotter,
but it's beef.
Now we're having afternoon tea.
What are you looking at?
I'm watching Beijing stores exploring.
Where do you want to go?
Strolling the Beijing Charm.
Take me for a stroll there.
An afternoon stroll?
Gecko Stroll.
Have you heard Gecko Stroll?
No.
You haven't heard Gecko Stroll?
You should have been born
when the song was released.
(Clueless)
I am a gecko waiting for mosquitoes.
You're a butterfly
fluttering gracefully.
When I was a kid, I watched
Pleasant Goat and Big Big Wolf.
Then what are you?
I'm Gray Wolf.
(Gray Wolf, Red Wolf)
You're Red Wolf.
I haven't seen it.
What I watched was...
Shaolin Wuzang?
The Story of Hongmao and Lantu?
Shuke and Beita.
Did you use QQ to 'steal' vegetables
when you were a kid?
Source text.
Yes.
You did 'steal' others' vegetables?
But my internet speed was terrible,
so basically, all my vegetables were...
Because at home,
to control my internet access,
my mom installed a dial-up connection.
Do you know what that means?
You could only go online
when there was a phone call.
Then what about your online dating?
It cut off any thoughts
of online dating.
She did a great job.
Let me do a cow impression for you.
How does a cow sound?
(Moo)
Let me do the Mickey Mouse Clubhouse.
Okay.
It's me.
Mickey Mouse Clubhouse.
(Got "killed")
Grandpa and Grandma are so happy.
They give me my favorite Xizhilang.
Keep it low-key.
Ruita (Wang Yi) suits hats.
Any hat suits you.
Now look at yours.
Let me offer you a pure white hada.
Now we're going to visit...
(Story)
Chen Jianying.
Yes. Bring...
Chen Jianying...
Some snacks.
Drop the handkerchief.
Chen Jianying.
Put it behind Chen Jianying.
Did Wentao rub off on you?
Everyone says
(Shared Brain)
candied haws taste sour.
Inside the sourness, there's a hint of
sweetness.
Hello.
Our afternoon tea,
seemingly healthy yet not really.
It looks so delicious.
Especially this durian.
Durian and mangosteen.
Durian, mangosteen and Greek yogurt.
And
passion fruit and peach.
Let's have a meal together.
We're gathering in Beijing.
Beijing.
Beijing welcomes you.
Beijing really has us two, huh?
Who exactly is there?
Who's there?
There's also Ji Yu.
Who's in Beijing? Ji Yu.
Beijing.
In Beijing,
(TT is me)
there is TT.
TT is there.
Now, on the way to the airport.
I'm heading back to Shanghai today.
I just counted.
We spent a total
of 16 days together this time.
Mr. Lu, how do you feel?
Sixteen days?
Yes.
I thought it was...
Like six days.
Yeah, I thought it was ten days.
But when I counted it
in the calendar memo,
I found 16 days.
Are you "annoyed"?
Not at all.
I feel like time flew by so fast.
(Steady happiness)
Keep up the good work.
PS,
if we count
from the burst light moment today,
it's been 100 days.
Exactly 100 days.
A hundred days.
But if we count
from the Confession Night...
There's still some time to go.
Still a few days away.
When I woke up this morning, I saw
videos our couple fans made.
I cried as I watched them.
I was really moved.
I'm very grateful to them.
They're so good at giving videos.
No, so good at making videos.
They're so talented.
We've received your overflowing love.
(A Day in the Life of Jia Peixuan)
(I'm Coming)
Okay.
After the morning
icebreaker activity,
I'll start my day.
(Reserved)
First, let me make myself
a cup of coffee.
(Dubbing)
I look so beautiful when I drink coffee.
(I'm so beautiful)
With the foam on my lips.
(Full of appreciation)
Okay, I'll play
with my kitten for a while.
The kitten is as big as my face.
My face is so small.
My face is actually
as small as the kitten.
Alright, kitty, skip the glamour.
I'll shine.
Okay, now I'm heading out to the gym
without eating anything.
So pretty.
(Admiring his girlfriend Admiring herself)
Pout.
(Xuan)
So pretty.
I'm so pretty.
(Continuing to admire his girlfriend)
Okay.
Usually, I come to the gym
mostly for taking photos
to admire my beauty.
I have no bad angles.
(Quick reaction)
How did I end up actually exercising?
I really came to work out.
Okay, I'll roll.
Let me relax my muscles first.
That angle just now wasn't right.
It made my head look big.
Now this angle
hits the perfect head-body proportion.
Yes.
Because refined people like us
(Refined)
need to consider
the camera presence constantly.
Yes.
I'll move a bit more.
Okay.
Now the waist-to-shoulder ratio
and the hip-to-leg ratio are perfect.
Okay.
Today, let's start with my first
gym move.
The first pose to strike
is the squat.
Squats
mainly target,
um,
the glutes and legs.
Okay.
I barely exercised anything.
But everyone knows
my purpose,
so I absolutely cannot skip
the photo-taking step.
Now I've opened my makeup bag.
I plan to start a refined day.
First, I randomly took out
something.
(Ranting skill: 100, Makeup knowledge: 0)
I'll apply it first.
Yes, I'll spread it evenly
on my face first.
Okay, here is a broken box.
(Broken box?)
Inside this box,
it should be...
(What is all this?)
I'll smile for a moment.
I won't tell you.
Yes, I took out a pair
of colored contacts.
Yes, this can make my pupils
infinitely larger.
Yes, look.
(You've got guts)
Now I just look cross-eyed.
Then, to avoid being cross-eyed,
I need to
put on the other one too.
Then I take out a pen.
On my lips,
apply another layer.
This is also
to make my lips
more rosy.
(My love)
Yes, to kiss you all.
Blink my eyes, act cute,
and act like a master.
Very good.
My makeup today is great.
Okay.
Then we're going to start
that second step of becoming beautiful.
That is, to make
a hairstyle.
So now, I randomly
apply some random stuff.
It doesn't matter.
Whatever.
It could be
water.
It could be snot.
(Nobody understands)
Whatever it could be.
Then we just
spread it evenly on the hair.
Now I'm in the basement garage
and pretend to be on a call.
But actually, this screen is wrong.
I didn't fake it successfully.
(Do I even need to pretend?)
But I'm now pretending
to be busy with business.
But I have no choice.
I don't need to pretend.
Because I have plenty of business.
Okay, now I'm sitting in my car.
In my daily life, I'm expressionless.
(Cold-faced beauty)
That's just how I am,
being an expressionless, cool beauty.
Okay, now I'm at the office.
Pretending to flip through
some documents.
This makes me look busier.
Taking a sip of water
from my big red water bottle.
Putting on my headphones.
Listening to whatever.
Mainly to strike
a pose.
I'm going to eat dinner.
Eating alone.
I'm going to starve to "death."
I'm starving to "death."
I was busy all day today.
I tossed my own takeout out,
thinking it was rubbish.
I really can't believe it.
I ordered a sandwich for myself.
And when I threw away the trash,
I threw it away along with the trash.
When
I got hungry at the office, I wondered
where my takeout was.
I can't believe myself.
Because usually,
for successful business people like us,
(Successful businesswoman)
when we're working,
we don't think about eating.
The busy work
makes us forget to eat.
Pretending to look at my phone.
Actually sneaking a glance
at the camera,
just to judge
if it's the right angle.
Now I'm inside the restaurant.
Look.
When I'm eating,
I still can't forget about work,
always holding a pen in my hand.
I'll definitely be writing something
with this pen.
Actually, I'm not working.
I'm writing a menu.
When the food is served,
what's the first step I do?
It's not eating.
Always remember, it's not eating.
It's letting who eat first.
Yes, the phone eats first.
Now I'm still
busy working while eating.
Okay, finally, after finishing the meal,
I'll check again
my makeup and styling for today.
So let my last smile
end my day.
Goodbye.
(Ling-Xi Duo's Daily Date)
(Xiamen Date)
This is
the park where we had our first date.
Let me show everyone.
Our first date in Xiamen.
Yes, the park where we had
our first date in Xiamen.
Listen.
Smiling until dawn.
They said that in the show,
I was sitting here wanting to kiss you.
I was licking my lips.
I said I'm done for.
I didn't say this trip is doomed.
Why?
Who wanted to kiss whom?
I don't know.
(Giving you a chance to rephrase)
Who wanted to kiss whom?
Me.
You what?
Can't say it.
Let's take a walk.
Okay.
This sea breeze
is very comfortable.
Very comfortable.
After coming to Xiamen,
your Mandarin is non-standard.
This is "when in Rome,
do as the Romans do."
After doing as the Romans do,
Top Grade A...
It becomes
Grade B.
Grade C.
Let's go home, baby.
We're going to have
Rapid Fire Q and A.
Okay.
Come on.
(Q: What was your first impression of me?)
What was your first impression of me?
(Instant answer)
Confident, cheerful, and sunny.
Before you met me,
(Q: Before you met me, what were your standards for a partner?)
what were your standards for a partner?
(Compatible personality)
At least a good personality.
(Q: What part of me attracts you the most?)
What part of me attracts you
the most?
(Crazily hinting)
Eyes, I guess.
(You pass)
Smile.
As for the part, your eyes.
After having a partner,
(Q: If a female confesses to you, how would you handle it?)
if a female confesses to you,
how would you handle it?
I'd definitely reject her
Would you, for me,
reject all ambiguous relationships?
Sure.
(Q: When was the best kiss experience?)
When was the best
kiss experience?
Why?
Tell everyone.
Handsome guy scratching his head.
No, this is your Rapid Fire Q and A.
That time at Youling's place.
(Q: After being with me, are you happier after than before?)
After being with me,
are you happier than before?
Yes.
Wait.
(Pfft)
I think this is very show-worthy.
Sorry, I ate BBQ tonight.
(Manual poison protection)
I'm scared.
(Human filter)
I'll suck it up.
Do not post this.
It must be edited in.
(Okay)
(Q: Do you ever envy others' girlfriends?)
Do you ever envy others' girlfriends?
No one would ever do that.
(Answer)
Do you envy?
I don't.
Because
(Is that the answer?)
I just don't envy.
Say the next line.
I'm waiting for the next line.
You ask me.
Come on, let me give you
a textbook-level answer.
(Do you ever envy others' boyfriends?)
Do you ever envy others'...
I don't.
Because my boyfriend
is the best in the world.
You just 'killed' the game.
I'll give you a chance.
Cut out my previous part.
Come on.
Next question: Do you ever envy others...
I don't.
Because my girlfriend
is the best in the world.
Alright.
Next page, you ask.
(Q: When I make you angry, how do you want me to comfort you?)
When I make you angry,
how do you want me to comfort you?
When you make me angry,
I hope you
will shamelessly coax me
until I'm better.
(Request received)
Received.
What do you most want to do
with me on a rainy day?
Get soaked in the rain together.
We'll just embrace the rain.
We just came back
from getting soaked in the rain.
When there is a torrential downpour,
we'll stand in the rain.
Let's do it together next time.
(Q: If you immigrated to Mars and could only bring three things, what would you choose?)
If you immigrated to Mars,
and could only bring three things,
what would you choose?
Ling Lizheng.
And what else? Mom and Dad.
(What about me?)
What about Ice Cream?
You should bring it.
Yes.
(Flawless)
What color and style of clothing
do you like me wearing the most?
It's hard to choose.
Hard to choose.
Because you look great
in whatever you wear.
(Killing the game again)
(Heading to the airport to return to Changsha)
Let's go.
Go.
You're leaving.
I know it's simple.
The sky in Xiamen today
is gray.
Because you're leaving.
We've arrived at the airport.
Well.
Blue sea, clear sky.
Xiamen Airport.
Starting to promote?
Welcomed by flight attendants
So close, so beautiful.
Weekend trip to Xiamen.
Beauty turns around.
Are you asking for my social account?
Not giving it.
I have a boyfriend.
(Already gave a boyfriend, do not disturb)
(Then I'll go?)
Then
who am I?
Summer break is over.
No, it's not.
It just started.
Going back to do homework.
Your summer break?
So rare.
You have summer break.
Your summer break and my summer break
seem different.
You cry even more than I do.
Goodbye.
(Boyfriend's POV)
Hui, you must be happy.
Huizi, what will I do when you leave?
(Passing through security)
(Preview)
Truth or Dare.
Wentao, take a sip of douzhi
and hold it in your mouth.
Yeah, who are you punishing?
Xuan, it's time to test
your physiological attraction.
Is it hot?
See, you're into this.
It's the taste of love.
(Who are you talking about?)
Lu Bingkun.
You two are enjoying yourselves.
Let everyone heat it up.
Baby, I miss you so much.
Today, we're doing
a Forbidden City makeover.
You're now under a 4x zoom lens.
Don't be so abstract.
Have I been downgraded already?
Haven't been home for a long time.
Apply nail polish
to this spirited lad.
Super sexy.
This is my first time
doing nails for a guy.
Are you satisfied with my service today?
You're someone who shows off your love.
I will.
Let me see your previous Moments posts.